<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<entry>
  <piece category="poem">
    <line>Because you were on the brink of something beautiful, but you couldn’t quite reach it and you fell too far</line>
    <author>Bianca Phipps</author>
    <title>Almosts</title>
  </piece>
  <piece category="poem">
    <line>I was carved hallow by loving hands hold wars in the spaces between my ribs</line>
    <author>Bianca Phipps</author>
    <title>Born To Embody It</title>
  </piece>  
  <piece category="poem">
    <line>You cannot break a mangled thing and you don’t know the last time your heart sounded like a heart</line>
    <author>Bianca Phipps</author>
    <title>The Heartbreaker piece</title>
  </piece>
  <piece category="poem">
    <line>When I sound like this I know my loved ones can find me</line>
    <author>Erin Schick</author>
    <title>Honest Speech</title>
  </piece>
  <piece category="poem">
    <line>When we are gone, what tangible life will be left?</line>
    <author>Ken Arkind</author>
    <title>David</title>
  </piece>
  <piece category="poem">
    <line>We all learned it from each other, the way each generation taught the next how to knit, weaving silence in between the threads</line>
    <author>Lily Myers</author>
    <title>shrinking Women</title>
  </piece>
  <piece category="poem">
    <line>We build bridges, we write books and hold grudges</line>
    <author>Meghann Plunkett</author>
    <title>Humans</title>
  </piece>
  <piece category="poem">
    <line>My heart would rattle and shake with all of the coins spilling back into it. I would stop digging around in my pockets for pieces of myself</line>
    <author>Melissa Lozada-Olivia</author>
    <title>If I Got Paid For All My Emotional Labor</title>
  </piece>
  <piece category="poem">
    <line>Ma mère n'a jamais eu des ailes</line>
    <author>Pages Matam</author>
    <title>Wings</title>
  </piece>
  <piece category="poem">
    <line>Know that your legs were made to run, your bones were made to heal</line>
    <author>Phil Kaye</author>
    <title>Beginning, Middle and End</title>
  </piece>
  <piece category="poem">
    <line>You make the same mistake over and over; you'll stop calling it a mistake</line>
    <author>Phil Kaye</author>
    <title>Repetition</title>
  </piece>
  <piece category="poem">
    <line>Strength from never being enough; healing from an open wound</line>
    <author>Samira Obeid</author>
    <title>Pigtails</title>
  </piece>
  <piece category="poem">
    <line>Because no matter how wide you stretch your fingers, your hands will always be too small to catch all the pain you want to heal.</line>
    <author>Sarah Kay</author>
    <title>If I Should Have A Daughter</title>
  </piece>
  <piece category="poem">
    <line>Instead, I said "it's okay."</line>
    <author>Sarah Kay</author>
    <title>Table Games</title>
  </piece>
</entry>